<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MT_1_u3031423</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_view">MT_1_u3031423</string>
    <string name="title_activity_card_details">MT_1_u3031423</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_card">MT_1_u3031423</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_image">MT_1_u3031423</string>
    <string name="app_title">Mobile technologies(8878) Business Card App</string>
    <string name="app_intro">The Business Card App allows a user to pick from existing Business Cards and edit the details, or upload a template by camera or download.</string>
    <string name="instruction_text">Tap Capture to take a phtoto of a Business Card or Tap Load to load one from memory</string>
    <string name="title_activity_report">Report</string>
    <string name="my_report">This report identifies the main concepts achieved
    for the purposes of assignment 1, Mobile Technologies. One key concept that is integral
    to the implementation is that of Intents. The Business Card App uses both implicit and explicit
    intents to communicate between modules. Explicit intents are those used to start a know activity whilst the explict
    can be used when the name of the particular component is unknown.

    The assignment requires the creation and manipulation of databases, this through leveraging existing libaries specificallly
        SqlLiteOpenHelper. Once the data base has been created it was then possible to leverage the ArrayAdaptor class to define custom versions
        and populate ListViews. The application also allows for the database to updated by, but not limited to
        the leveraging of Bundles, which act as way to communicate data to a new activty.

        The application implements menu usage and I have tried to moderate layout inconsistencies by setting global
        dimensions. Some of these dimensions are similar to that used in HTML such as H1, H2 and paragraph.
        These dimensions can be found in res/values/dimens.

        Testing has been completed on emulated Nexus 5x and Nexus 6p, API 24.
        Testing has been completed on Chuwi Vi7, Api 19.





    </string>






</resources>
